<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="change_2_0_1">
        <b>Fixes</b>\n\n
        • Fix bug where description text sometimes would get cut off
    </string>

    <string name="change_2_0_0">
        <b><i>Daily wallpaper changer</i></b>\n\n
        Daily wallpapers were the most requested feature, now they\'re finally here! The next screen will tell you more about the feature. It is disabled by default.
        If you encounter any unexpected behaviour, please email me.\n\n

        <b><i>Launcher widget</i></b>\n\n
        • A launcher widget for <b>APOD Gallery</b> has been implemented.\n
        • Swipe through all of the images you\'ve saved from <b>APOD Gallery</b>.\n
        • Tap on a particular image in the widget to open the app to the corresponding date.\n\n

        <b>Other additions</b>\n\n
        • Add new changelog dialog (this thing)\n
        • Landscape support for all devices\n\n

        <b>Fixes</b>\n\n
        • Fix HTTPS issue on older devices and reinstate support for pre-Lollipop devices\n
        • Display proper images titles for dates before 1998\n
        • Adjust toolbar text colours on older devices\n
        • Update libraries\n
        • Improve timeout handling\n
        • Improve permission management for devices on Marshmallow and above\n
        • Improve rendering of image description\n\n

        I take each reviews and suggestion into consideration. If you haven\'t yet, I encourage you to leave a review in the Play Store.
    </string>

    <string name="wallpaper_summary">The service checks if a new image is available every day and set the current day\'s featured image as your phone\'s wallpaper.\n\n
        It will automatically run on boot. The wallpaper is not changed if the current day\'s featured content is not a picture.\n\n

        <b>Warning</b>: This may use your mobile data connection. Images are usually less than 1 megabyte.\n
        <b>Warning</b>: Task killers and memory management apps may conflict with the wallpaper changer task. I suggest whitelisting <b>APOD Gallery</b> if you want to enable this feature.\n
    </string>
</resources>