<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="change_latest">
        <b>Changes</b>\n
        - Improve scrolling through description text\n
        - Improve compatibility with Android P
    </string>
    <string name="change_2_0_14">
        <b>Updates</b>\n
        - Update crash logging tool\n
        - Improvements to first-time launch\n
        - Improvements to wallpaper changer
    </string>
    <string name="change_2_0_13">
        <b>Fixes</b>\n
        - Fix crashes when viewing certain non-image content\n
        - Prevent multiple dialogs from showing\n
        - Prevent other dialogs from showing on top of "What's New" dialog
    </string>
    <string name="change_2_0_12">
        <b>Updates</b>\n
        - Update libraries\n
        - Improve daily wallpaper changer\n
    </string>
    <string name="change_2_0_11">
        <b>Fixes</b>\n
        - Fix problems adding widgets on Android 4.x devices\n\n
        <b>Updates</b>\n
        - Update Android libraries (improved compatibility)\n\n
        APOD Gallery is no longer in active development. You will see fewer updates, however I will continue to fix any bugs or crashes that arise. Thank you!\n
    </string>
    <string name="change_2_0_10">
        <b>Fixes</b>\n
        - Fix rare crash during permissions request dialog\n\n
        <b>Changes</b>\n
        - Add Android O support\n\n
        Please report any bugs you encounter.\n
    </string>
    <string name="change_2_0_9">
        <b>Changes</b>\n
        - Update support libraries\n
    </string>
    <string name="change_2_0_8">
        <b>Changes</b>\n
        - Improve compatibility for older devices\n
        - Add clearer error messages\n
        - Change default save directory to use device-specific external storage path\n
        <b>Fixes</b>\n
        - Fix crash when tapping widget\n
    </string>
    <string name="change_2_0_7">
        <b>Improvements</b>\n
        - Update support libraries\n
    </string>
    <string name="change_2_0_6">
        <b>Fixes</b>\n
        - Fix app widget where pictures were not being retrieved properly\n
    </string>
    <string name="change_2_0_5">
        <b>Changes</b>\n
        - Automatically restart daily wallpaper changer (if enabled) after each app update\n\n
        <b>Fixes</b>\n
        - Wallpaper was not changing for some users, should be working now!\n
    </string>
    <string name="change_2_0_4">
        <b>Fixes</b>\n
        - Fix SSL bug where older devices (pre-Lollipop) could not retrieve images from NASA\'s servers\n
        - Improve how wallpapers are downloaded for the daily wallpaper changer\n
    </string>
    <string name="change_2_0_2"><b>Attention widget users</b>\n
        It is highly recommended that you remove and re-add the APOD Gallery widget as some new bug fixes have been implemented.\n\n
        <b>Changes</b>\n
        <i>Widget</i> - Max image limit capped at 20\n
        <i>Widget</i> - Default limit set to 10\n
        <i>Widget</i> - Every time you save a new image in APOD Gallery, all the app widgets will be automatically updated (max image limit will be respected)\n\n

        <b>Fixes</b>\n
        <i>Widget</i> - Fix crash due to lack of Storage permission\n\n

        If you see a <b>"No images found"</b> message on the widget, either there are no images saved in your save folder, or you do not have Storage permissions enabled for <b>APOD Gallery</b>.\n
    </string>

    <string name="change_2_0_1">
        <b>Fixes</b>\n
        • <i>General</i> - Fix bug where description text sometimes would get cut off\n
        • <i>General</i> - Fix logging errors\n
        • <i>Widget</i> - Correctly retrieves images from save directory\n
    </string>

    <string name="change_2_0_0">
        <b><i>Daily wallpaper changer</i></b>\n\n
        Daily wallpapers were the most requested feature, now they\'re finally here! The next screen will tell you more about the feature. It is disabled by default.
        If you encounter any unexpected behaviour, please email me.\n\n

        <b><i>Launcher widget</i></b>\n\n
        • A launcher widget for <b>APOD Gallery</b> has been implemented.\n
        • Swipe through all of the images you\'ve saved from <b>APOD Gallery</b>.\n
        • Tap on a particular image in the widget to open the app to the corresponding date.\n\n

        <b>Other additions</b>\n\n
        • Add new changelog dialog (this thing)\n
        • Landscape support for all devices\n\n

        <b>Fixes</b>\n\n
        • Fix HTTPS issue on older devices and reinstate support for pre-Lollipop devices\n
        • Display proper images titles for dates before 1998\n
        • Adjust toolbar text colours on older devices\n
        • Update libraries\n
        • Improve timeout handling\n
        • Improve permission management for devices on Marshmallow and above\n
        • Improve rendering of image description\n\n

        I take each reviews and suggestion into consideration. If you haven\'t yet, I encourage you to leave a review in the Play Store.
    </string>

    <string name="wallpaper_summary">The service checks if a new image is available every day and set the current day\'s featured image as your phone\'s wallpaper.\n\n
        It will automatically run on boot. The wallpaper is not changed if the current day\'s featured content is not a picture.\n\n

        <b>Warning</b>: This may use your mobile data connection. Images are usually less than 1 megabyte.\n
        <b>Warning</b>: Task killers and memory management apps may conflict with the wallpaper changer task. I suggest whitelisting <b>APOD Gallery</b> if you want to enable this feature.\n
    </string>
</resources>